[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
You have so many transactions
you need to close today.
Mariano and I worked hard
to grow all of this.
So, I want you...
to prioritize the business!
Django, it's rumored that Gabo
took Binoy, Tolits, and Daboy.
They're part oh his circle now!
You should stop Gabo
before he becomes well-known.
We'll strengthen
our forces, Pa.
I'll make sure
he won't make a move.
Alpha one, on-site.
What's your status?
Alpha two, in position.
Positive.
Mr. Chan is inside.
We called in
as potential buyers.
The vendor said she
will ask her boss first.
What if we split
into two groups?
Let's come up
with our own gimmick
so we don't look
stupid standing here.
No, this is what we'll do.
We're on the other side.
Won't we have a hard time
with this, ma'am?
The case we are handling
is too heavy.
We need to follow him,
then we'll entrap him there.
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Hey, what's going on?
- Have you seen him?
- No.
We need to catch Tiger.
We need to follow Mr. Chan
because he's going
to take us to Tiger.
The people's way
of thinking is--
[ARNEL] Let's go.
Let's go back to the office.
- Let's go. [GROANS]
- in Ginintuang Lupa.
Hey, stop looking
at your phone. Let's go.
[DOOR SLIDES, CLOSES]
What are you watching?
Sir, isn't this
what we're covering?
- Here. Take a look.
- it's for Ginintuang Lupa.
Not only do they lack
common sense,
they also have
no breeding!
Can you believe
that when we went there
with the owner
of Ginintuang Lupa,
we were beaten
and pelted with stones?
Don't they know that
he is a retired general!
A little respect, please.
- Wow.
- Hey.
People of Ginintuang Lupa,
- that land isn't yours!
- Oli.
Find out who that general is
who owns Ginintuang Lupa.
- [ARNEL] Let's go.
- [ENGINE HUMMS]
[ESTRELLA] Ma'am.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Watch this.
[SALVADOR] There are so many
questions that needs answers.
after we interviewed
a woman whose husband,
Rudy Magtibay,
is currently in critical
condition at the hospital.
After being shot
during this demolition,
the public's questions
are heating up even more...
why does someone
have to get hurt?
In a demolition led
by the police,
one question remains
in the family's mind,
who fired the shot?
Who is to blame for this?
That Salvador is really
going too far.
He won't stop until
he ruins NLEA.
He's even working with them!
[ESTRELLA] Ma'am,
if i'm being honest,
what he said is true.
What do you mean?
[ESTRELLA] In the demolition,
there was police
brutality involved.
Severe police brutality!
So you're saying...
that we are the ones
who shot the victim?
That's what I can't tell.
But in my eyes,
we overstepped.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS] Argh!
[SALVADOR] While the victim
is fighting for their life,
his family is waiting
for an answer.
- Who fired the shot?
- [MAX] Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
- May I speak to you?
Lieutenant Jacinto,
what is it about?
About the excessive violence
during the demolition, sir.
That would ruin the image
of the police.
Someone could've died!
We overstepped, sir!
Sit down, Lieutenant.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Before you scold me...
and before you call me names,
let's not forget
who ordered the demolition
in Gininutang Lupa.
it's your father, isn't it?
Your father needs
to be held accountable.
Your father is just
as responsible.
Now.
If you really love your father,
and I believe you do.
My advice?
Shut up, Lieutenant Jacinto.
Just shut up.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TOTO] Sweetie! Sweetie!
Look at this!
Please don't call me
Sweetie.
- What's that?
- Here! Look!
They just released it!
[BETCHAY] We need your help!
We can't afford t
he medical bill!
[SALVADOR] While the victim
fights for his life,
his family waits for answers.
Who pulled the trigger, and why
did what should have been
an enforcement of the law
end in bloodshed?
We will never stop pursuing this
until whoever is responsible
is held accountable.
Oh no,
Sir needs to know about this!
- Give it to me!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Sweetie, stop right there!
Let's not be stuck up!
This is bad news!
Who do you think they'll blame
when they watch that video?
That's scary.
It's a problem.
Why do we have to hide it?
Don't you see?
This is bad news!
We shouldn't be the ones
to tell them.
Let them find out on their own.
Four thousand.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[CRYING]
What if...
we don't get enough money
for Rudy's operation?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if he dies? [CRYING]
I can't handle it...
I don't think I can, Mameng!
I don't think I can
handle losing him!
He's the only man I ever loved!
He's the only man I love!
I don't think I can lose him!
[MAMENG] Betchay...
C'mon...
don't be like that.
Nothing bad will happen to Rudy.
Gabo already has a job.
He'll find a way!
We can save Rudy!
It's always Gabo!
It's always Gabo! Gabo! Gabo!
I don't believe
that he can help us!
C'mon, Mameng!
He's your brother!
He might die
if we don't get the money!
Will anybody help us?!
It's always me! It's always me!
I'll find a way.
What will you do?
Anything!
I'll do anything to save Rudy.
Even if I sell my own body!
Betchay.
[SIGHS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS CLOSE]
- Hey!
- Ooh!
- Come drop by BeerGin!
- Hey, you, come visit!
- We have a promo going on!
- Don't worry!
[ROSANNA] The night is long.
- [PRISCILLA GROANS]
- [JOYCE] Mm-hmm.
- Just relax, girls.
- Hey, come in!
- Oh, Betchay!
- Oh!
How's Rudy doing?
Uh...
Was he able to get
an operation?
Not yet. We still don't have
enough money
so he's still unconscious.
But is he doing alright?
[SIGHS] He's in the ICU,
in critical condition.
Oh, that's very unfortunate.
Yeah...
You know how hospitals work,
they're like taxis.
It gets more expensive
as you go.
Not to mention he's in the ICU
so the bills just get bigger.
It isn't much but I hope
you accept this, Betchay.
- Oh, really?
- Here, Betchay.
- Oh, thank you, guys!
- It's not much, Betchay.
Oh, I'm not going to say no
to these!
Thank you so much to all of you!
By the way, how are things
going here at the bar?
Why? Are you doing a survey?
Come on, I'm just asking.
Oh, just ignore her. She's just
mad it's a slow day today.
Our only customers right now
are Boss Paquito
and his friends.
[WHISPERING] Paquito's here?
Perfect! I actually came here
to visit him.
Are you gonna borrow money
from him?
Oh, Betchay, you could get
in trouble
because of what Gabo did.
Screw it! He's the only one
who could give me what I need.
A job!
Come on, Betchay,
with that body of yours
I don't think you can
break into a house anymore!
Oh, not that!
I was going to ask Paquito
if I could work here in BeerGin.
Can you handle it? Will Rudy
even allow you to work
as a hostess?
Well, it used to be my job
anyway.
Plus,
I'm doing this for his sake.
Alright, then.
- Welcome. Head inside.
- Oh!
- Hmm...
- Hey!
[PAQUITO] But,
always keep this in mind,
don't even try to fool me
because...
you know me.
We won't do shady business
behind you, Paquito.
Nothing gets past you!
- Well, then. Jack!
- Boss?
Escort them out.
Yes, boss. Follow me
this way, please.
Boss, someone wants
to talk to you.
Here comes the divas!
[BETCHAY GIGGLING AWKWARDLY]
Hey, Paquito!
Betchay, how can I help you?
- I'm just wondering if--
- [ROSANNA] Boss!
She's looking for a job.
[ROSANNA] Take her in!
Come on!
Oh, Betchay...
your family committed
an offense against ours.
How bold of you
to even come to me.
Come on, Paquito.
- Hm?
- Whatever happened
between Gabo and Django
has nothing to do with me!
- Huh?
- We're not related by blood!
That's why we have different
personalities.
- He's not right in the head
- Mm-hmm...
but I am. Come on...
The favor I'm asking for
isn't for Gabo's sake.
[STUTTERING] I-- it's for me!
Rudy just really needs it!
- For his funeral!
- For the hospital!
- Stop teasing, Paquito!
- [ROSANNA LAUGHING]
Come on, I'm begging
on my knees here!
- [PAQUITO LAUGHS]
- Just get her the job, man.
She used to be a hostess
back in the day, right?
But she's already
lost her touch!
[ROSANNA] Oh, boss, you...
Wait, you're right.
Don't get cocky! You...
Alright, alright.
I'll give you a chance.
If someone books you tonight,
you're hired.
[CLAPS] Thank you!
- I'll give it my all! I swear!
- [PAQUITO LAUGHS]
Oh, Betchay,
if you don't secure a customer,
you know what that means,
don't you?
[PAQUITO LAUGHS]
Well then,
- Osang, I'll leave her to you.
- Yes, boss.
- Then, bye!
- Okay, boss!
- Bye, divas!
- There.
The boss took Betchay in.
As if we aren't struggling
enough!
- Leave her alone.
- Hmph!
Betchay is in need right now!
- [BETCHAY] Mm-hmm.
- That's right!
Come on, stop acting
like a stranger!
Aren't we all struggling here?
Let's give and take!
I'm not going to steal
your regulars from you.
You won't be able
to snatch them away anyway.
Okay, enough! The more,
the merrier, okay?
Let's get to work!
Don't mind these girls!
Enough chatting! Go! Go!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Gentlemen!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Sir, I'll go with you!
We have men doing
the collecting tonight, Colonel.
Good. Business should
flow continuously.
[UMALI] Sir, what's the matter?
General, please-- Is there
something the matter?
- General Duran--
- [THUDS]
[GROANS, INHALES SHARPLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Leave the room.
- No.
I want your subordinates to hear
just what kind of leader
you are.
You've been keeping up
with the defamatory reports
against us, I presume?
I am, General. For now--
- And you're just sitting here?!
- No, sir.
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS, INHALES SHARPLY]
- [DOMINGO GROANS]
- [GENERAL DURAN GRUNTS]
You're letting our institution's
name get tarnished.
No, I don't, General.
That's not true.
The public is once again
wary against the police force.
One wrong move
and everyone suffers for it.
Explain to me how things
got to this point.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
General Duran,
we did everything we could.
We exercised maximum tolerance.
We followed the guidelines--
But a civilian was shot!
There's a story circulating
to tarnish the image
of the police.
[GENERAL DURAN SIGHS]
- The truth is, General--
- The truth is...
I don't think
you are a capable leader.
[EXHLAES SHAKILY]
I don't know how you'll fix this
but you better fix it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[PRIEST] To love and to cherish,
till death do us part.
May you all be filled with joy,
and your hearts with love.
[PHONE CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC
PLAYING]
[GUESTS APPLAUDING]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[LAO] Boss,
thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming, sir.
- Where's your wife?
- Over there, sir.
Still humoring her relatives.
Norris.
Give this to her. It's my gift.
Congratulations.
Thank you, boss. Thank you.
Now that you're wedded,
you might lose your edge.
Boss, that's impossible.
I owe your brother a lot.
I'll never leave
the group behind.
Anyway. Boss, I'll just go back.
- I'll just visit my wife.
- [PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Ma?
Are you on your way
to meet the buyer?
Uh... I'm still at the wedding.
Are we right on schedule?
Why did you even
prioritize that?
Okay. We'll be on our way.
[PHONE BEEPING]
- Stallone.
- Boss.
Tell Lao we'll be on our way
to meet Mr. Chan.
Yes, boss.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
If this doesn't go smoothly...
[DEBORAH SIGHS]
You should've just let Lucas
take care of this.
I told you, Lucas
is still not ready.
Just trust Victor.
He can manage all of this soon.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
- [CAR HORN HONKS]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KAREN] It's getting late.
Some stores are already closing
and we still haven't gotten
a visual on Mr. Chan.
[SEBASTIAN] Sam,
can you hear me?
What's your status over there?
Maybe the target already left.
Don't worry.
We're covering all possible
exit points.
[IPE] Gabo.
Is Mr. Chan really in there?
What if we're just wasting
our time out here?
Nothing we can do about it.
This is my job.
I need to find him.
We'll just have to wait here...
until we find Mr. Chan.
Because he's the only one
who could tell us...
who Tiger is.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Victor!
[VICTOR] Mr. Chan!
We're about to leave
the wedding.
We're on our way to the bar.
[MR. CHAN] Okay.
- I'll see you. [JINGLING]
- Alright!
One of my people, Lee,
is already there.
She'll take care of you, okay?
[MR. CHAN] Okay. Thank you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
Alright, here's the plan.
I'll go inside and check if
Mr. Chan is still there.
Okay. Be careful.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I have an idea.
Tekla, go inside and find out
if Mr. Chan is in there.
Hey, wait.
I'm going there alone?
You're not coming with me?
You can do it.
It'd be better if you
go there alone.
If we go as a group,
they might get suspicious
and our plan could fail.
Go.
Alright. I'm going in.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Hi!
- Can I see this one?
- Sure.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- This is pretty.
- Mm-hmm.
- How much is it?
- Let me check the price.
Fifty-four thousand two
hundred forty pesos.
Fifty-four thousand--
You see, miss...
- I own a business.
- Oh.
I was hoping to get a discount
if I buy in bulk.
Can I talk to your boss?
Oh, sure. I'll call Mr. Chan.
Just a sec.
Shiela, can you please
assist her?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAM] Thank you.
- [SAM] Can I see this one too?
- [SHIELA] Okay, ma'am.
Wow! That's beautiful, miss!
How much is this?
Does it look good on me?
Excuse me.
That's reserved for me.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, really?
I don't see any name
on it.
- How come it's reserved?
- I'm going to buy it.
[SCOFFS] You're so cocky.
What, you think you're pretty
and all that?
Hey, you're just taller than me,
but I can compete with you.
What?
You know what, miss?
If you'll just cause a scene,
you better stay away.
[CHUCKLES] Don't talk to me
in English.
We're not in America.
And why are you wearing
a jacket? It's hot here.
[STAFF] Miss, please don't
make a scene here.
- I can kick you out of here.
- Yes, please. You do that.
Hey! You're all arrogant!
Stop acting all high
and mighty!
- Call the security.
- How dare you?!
- Guard! Guard!
- Call the guard.
- She's causing a scene.
- No, I'm not!
She started it! I was just
looking at jewelry!
- Please go outside.
- No! I'm not causing a scene!
- Take her outside.
- Don't touch me!
- Where's the owner?! Hey!
- That's enough, ma'am.
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's go.
Faster, faster. Let's go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Just leave. Come on.
- I said let me go!
Mr. Chan, there's someone
causing trouble here.
- Who's that?
- A customer.
Hey! I'm not causing
trouble, Mr. Chan!
I'm a customer but they're
kicking me out!
Get out! Get out!
[TEKLA] You arrogant people!
Hi, sir. I'm Carlota Diaz.
I have an online business
and stalls in the province.
Looks like Tekla got busted.
[TEKLA] Ow!
[SAM] I was thinking maybe
if I order in bulk,
maybe you could give me
a discount?
Okay. But not today.
I have a meeting
at Jade Imperial.
I'll give you my number.
Call me tomorrow
or anytime, okay?
[TEKLA] Hmph!
I'll give you my card.
We'll talk tomorrow or
next time. But not today.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- What happened?
- [TEKLA] Gabo!
[SIGHS SHARPLY] There's this
pale-looking girl inside
who acted like she's bought
the whole store.
You started another fight?
What about Gabo's task
for you?
Yes, I started fight!
But I only did that
to lure the owner out.
- Ha!
- Then, what happened?
It's confirmed!
It was Mr. Chan.
I saw him with my own eyes.
But I think he was
on his way out.
He mentioned a
business meeting at...
Jade... Jade Imperial?
Team, the target
is on his way out.
Visuals on target.
I repeat, visuals on target.
Gabo! That's him!
Over there! That's Mr. Chan!
In the red sunglasses!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's follow him.
- Where's Daboy?
- He's at his post.
Call him.
I'll just get my bike.
I'll see you at Jade Imperial.
- Go.
- [TEKLA] Okay.
- I'll call him.
- Copy. See you later.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Tekla.
- Hey, fart face!
Where are you?
"Fart face?"
We're at our post.
Gabo's looking for you.
We found Mr. Chan.
- We're going to follow him.
- [BUSY TONE]
Where's Binoy?
He went to take a piss
ages ago.
Does he have a bladder problem?
Let's go get him.
- Wait!
- Tekla called. Come on!
Let's go.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Follow Mr. Chan.
I'll be right behind you.
Copy.
Let's move!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll settle with the family
of the gunshot victim.
They're in the wrong!
Now, they're whining online?!
They won't stop. Looks like
they're demanding money.
You need money, right?
You know, Betchay, I've always
had my eyes on you.
I've liked you
since we were kids.
The target is locked
on the enemy.
[ENGINE ROARS]
If you see Tiger, alert us.
- Why didn't you go inside?
- They require a... QT?
It's QR! Stupid!
We need to get in.
Find a way to get inside.
The two groups
are in position,
so this Thursday...
Looks like they're
a big-time syndicate.
They're heavily armed, while
we're coming in empty-handed.
Brace yourselves for chaos.
NCIA! Hands in the air,
Victor Zafra!
[GUNSHOTS]
[CLAMORING]
- [ENGINE REVS]
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Follow them!